American Colonization Society Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
American Colonization Society Records 1792-1964 (bulk 1823-1912)
MSS10660
American Colonization Society
190,000 items 717 containers 168 linear feet 331 microfilm reels
Manuscript Division Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Organizational records of the society, including correspondence, financial and business papers, reports, and miscellaneous material relating to administrative and financial matters, membership, slavery and the status of slaves in the pre-Civil War period, and emigration, colonization, and education in Liberia. Includes the personal papers of William McLain and letterbooks of the Massachusetts Colonization Society.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
People
Ashmun, J. (Jehudi), 1794-1828--Correspondence.; Benson, Stephen Allen, 1816-1865--Correspondence.; Buchanan, Thomas, d. 1841--Correspondence.; Cresson, Elliott, 1796-1854--Correspondence.; Hazard, Thomas R. (Thomas Robinson), 1797-1886--Correspondence.; Latrobe, John H. B. (John Hazlehurst Boneval), 1803-1891--Correspondence.; Lugenbeel, J. W. (James Washington), 1819?-1857--Correspondence.; McLain, William. William McLain papers. 1831-1850.; Roberts, Joseph J. (Joseph Jenkins), 1809-1876--Correspondence.; Smith, Gerrit, 1797-1874--Correspondence.
Organizations
American Colonization Society.; Massachusetts Colonization Society. Massachusetts Colonization Society letterbooks. 1856-1875.
Subjects
African Americans--Colonization--Africa.; Education--Liberia.; Freedmen--Colonization--Africa, West.; Slavery--United States.
Places
Liberia--Colonization.
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records of the American Colonization Society were given to the Library of Congress by the society in 1913 and 1964-1965.
Additional Guides
In 1979, the Library published The American Colonization Society, a Register of Its Records in the Library of Congress.
Transfers
Items have been transferred from the Manuscript Division to other custodial divisions of the Library Photographs have been transferred to the Prints and Photographs Division. Maps have been transferred to the Geography and Map Division. All transfers are identified in these divisions as part of the records of the American Colonization Society.
Access and Restrictions
The records of the American Colonization Society are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Microfilm
A microfilm edition of these papers is available on 331 reels. Consult a reference librarian in the Manuscript Division concerning availability for purchase or interlibrary loan. To promote preservation of the originals, researchers are required to consult the microfilm edition as available.
Chronology of Events
Date Event
1816 Meetings held at Washington, D.C., to discuss forming a colonization society
1817 “The American Society for Colonizing Free People of Colour of the United States” founded at Washington, D.C., with Bushrod Washington as president and Elias B. Caldwell as secretary Ebenezer Burgess and Samuel J. Mills sent to Africa to select a suitable site for the colony
1820 First colonists sent to Africa where they resided at Sierra Leone
1821 Eli Ayres and Robert Stockton purchased land for a colony at Cape Mesurado on the west coast of Africa
1822 Ralph R. Gurley elected secretary of the society First settlers established at Cape Mesurado Jehudi Ashmun arrived in Africa and became the society's first colonial agent (died 1828)
1824 Ralph R. Gurley visited the colonists Territory of new colony named Liberia; settlement named Monrovia
1825 Publication of the first issue of the society's journal, African Repository
1837 American Colonization Society incorporated in Maryland
1837-1839 Society reorganized; new constitution adopted Samuel Wilkeson named president of the board of directors and general agent in charge of administration (resigned 1841) Ralph R. Gurley named corresponding secretary
1839 Commonwealth of Liberia organized under a governor appointed by the society Thomas Buchanan named governor of Liberia (died 1841)
1841 Joseph Jenkins Roberts named governor of Liberia
1844 William McLain elected secretary of the society
1847 Liberia declared independence; Joseph Jenkins Roberts chosen president
1857 Republics of Liberia and Maryland in Liberia united
1858 William McLain elected financial secretary and treasurer of the society (died 1873)
1862 United States formally recognized Liberia
1873 William Coppinger elected financial secretary and treasurer (died 1892)
1912-1913 Society's active support of emigration ceased
1929 Booker Washington Agriculture and Industrial Institute founded in Kakata, Liberia, largely supported by the American Colonization Society and the Phelps-Stokes Fund
1954 Booker Washington Institute became a technical college attached to the University of Liberia, Kakata, Liberia
1963 Directors voted to dissolve the society; functions ceased
1964 American Colonization Society legally dissolved; assets turned over to the Phelps-Stokes Fund
Scope and Content Note
The records of the American Colonization Society span the years 1792-1964, with the bulk of the material concentrated in the period 1823-1912. The records include a variety of material, but in terms of content and physical size the various correspondence series predominate. The society's major interests and activities changed in emphasis during its long history, and this change is reflected in the voluminous correspondence, which ranges in subject from routine administrative and financial matters to the problems of slavery, the status of slaves and freedmen in society, and the advantages and disadvantages of emigration and colonization. The collection is organized in seven series: Incoming Correspondence, Outgoing Correspondence, General Correspondence, Financial Papers, Business Papers, Subject File, and Miscellany.
During the decades prior to the Civil War, the society sought to implement its solution to the slavery problem – colonization of Negroes in Africa – by establishing the colony of Liberia on the west coast of Africa and raising money to transport and support emigrants. Also during this period the society came under attack from critics, particularly William Lloyd Garrison and other abolitionists, who termed it proslavery and succeeded in winning over some previously ardent colonizationists, notably Gerrit Smith, a major contributor to the society's efforts prior to 1835. The efforts of the society to maintain neutrality on the slavery issue and to appeal to all sections of the country are also reflected in the correspondence. Notable correspondents of the pre-Civil War period include Lyman Hotchkiss Atwater, Benjamin Coates, Elliott Cresson, John H. Eaton, Henry Leavitt Ellsworth, Reverend R. S. Finley, Thomas R. Hazzard, Silas Howe, John H. B. Latrobe, John Maclean, and Anson Greene Phelps. An index to incoming correspondence for the period 1839-1855 is located in at the end of the Domestic Letters subseries of the Incoming Correspondence series.
Correspondence in the collection also reveals the difficulty the society experienced in obtaining funds to carry on its work. Letters document the largely unsuccessful efforts to get financial aid from the United States Congress and state legislatures, and reports received from agents around the country attest to the difficulty in obtaining individual contributions and the lack of cooperation from various state auxiliaries.
After the Civil War, the society's activities centered primarily on helping people who wished to emigrate and on providing funds for their support after arrival in Liberia. The correspondence, accordingly, is concerned mainly with obtaining funds for these purposes through private contributions and with counseling those who wished to emigrate. Letters requesting help in moving to Liberia are numerous until 1910, when the activity of the society in this area diminished. Lists of applicants for passage to Liberia appear in the correspondence during the late-nineteenth century as well as in separate registers and rolls contained in the Subject File series. Major figures in the society in this later period were William Coppinger and William McLain. Correspondents include D. C. Haynes, John H. B. Latrobe, John Orcutt, and Joseph Tracy. A large number of communications are from the firm of Yates & Porterfield of New York, through which the society arranged passage to Liberia for the emigrants.
After the turn of the century the society was primarily concerned with the support of education in Liberia, and correspondence is devoted chiefly to administrative and financial matters, particularly cooperation with the Phelps-Stokes Fund in support of the Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute founded at Kakata, Liberia, in 1929.
Throughout its history, the society received reports from Liberia telling of the conditions of the various settlements. Some of the earliest letters were written by Jehudi Ashmun, one of the society's first agents in Liberia, describing the progress and problems of the colony in 1823 and the need for American support. Later reports and dispatches from the colony come from Stephen Benson, Thomas Buchanan, first governor of Liberia under the commonwealth system, Edward W. Blyden, J. W. Lugenbeel, and Joseph Jenkins Roberts (1809-1876), who became the first president of the Republic of Liberia in 1847. There is also correspondence from ordinary settlers in which they relate their travel experiences, describe the settlements they established or into which they moved, and discuss future plans.
Additional records documenting the administrative functions of the society include financial ledgers, account books, and registers of names of contributors and subscribers to the African Repository, the society's journal. The original books of minutes and proceedings of the meetings of the society are also in the records as are drafts and manuscript copies of many of the annual reports. Letters from society members and reports from Liberia were often reprinted in the African Repository and annual reports. Many letters for the period prior to 1823 survive only in this form. A few letters printed in the annual reports of 1819-1821 were preserved by Peter Force, then printer for the society; these now form part of the Peter Force Papers in the Manuscript Division.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in seven series:
I: Incoming Correspondence, 1819-1917
II: Outgoing Correspondence, 1839-1912
III: General Correspondence, 1909-1965
IV: Financial Papers, 1818-1963
V: Business Papers, 1816-1963
VI: Subject File, 1792-1964
VII: Miscellany, 1835-1935
http://lccn.loc.gov/mm78010660
Container List
Available on microfilm. Shelf no. 14,745
- I: Incoming Correspondence, 1819-1917 (Box I:A1-I:E5, Reel 1-181)
  - A: Domestic Letters, 1823-1912 (Box I:A1-I:A298, Reel 1-153)
    Letters received by the society from within the United States concerning all areas in which the society was involved and letters from Liberia before 1833. Subjects include memberships, contributions, finances, emigration, and the African Repository, as well as the views of the society's officers and members on the question of slavery and the position of slaves and free blacks in the United States.
    Correspondence is bound in volumes and generally arranged in chronological order. Most of the volumes dated after 1839-1840 contain an alphabetical index to the letters within.
    - 1823, July 17-1926, Nov. 12 (Box I:A1, Reel 1)
    - 1826, Nov. 14-1827, Jan. 19 (Box I:A2, Reel 1)
    - 1827 (Box I:A3, Reel 1)
      - Jan. 20-Mar. 20
      - Mar. 21-June 28 (Box I:A4, Reel 2)
      - June 29-Aug. 14 (Box I:A5, Reel 2)
      - Aug. 15-Oct. 21 (Box I:A6, Reel 2)
      - Oct. 22-Dec. 11 (Box I:A7, Reel 3)
    - 1827, Dec. 12-1828, Feb. 9 (Box I:A8, Reel 3)
    - 1828 (Box I:A9, Reel 3)
      - Feb. 12-May 5
      - May 7-Aug. 4 (Box I:A10, Reel 4)
      - Aug. 5-Oct. 19 (Box I:A11, Reel 4)
      - Oct. 20-Dec. 27 (Box I:A12, Reel 4)
    - 1828, Dec. 29-1829, Feb. 7 (Box I:A13, Reel 5)
    - 1829 (Box I:A14, Reel 5)
      - Feb. 9-Apr. 27
      - Apr. 28-June 26 (Box I:A15, Reel 5)
      - June 29-July 21 (Box I:A16, Reel 6)
      - July 22-Aug. 25 (Box I:A17, Reel 6)
      - Aug. 26-Oct. 31 (Box I:A18, Reel 6)
      - Nov. 1-Dec. 19 (Box I:A19, Reel 7A)
    - 1829, Dec. 21-1830, Feb. 11 (Box I:A20, Reel 7B)
    - 1830 (Box I:A21, Reel 7B)
      - Feb. 12-Mar. 31
      - Apr. 1-June 1 (Box I:A22, Reel 8)
      - June 2-July 6 (Box I:A23, Reel 8)
      - July 7-15 (Box I:A24, Reel 8)
      - July 16-Aug. 8 (Box I:A25, Reel 9)
      - Aug. 9-31 (Box I:A26, Reel 9)
      - Sept. 1-Oct. 5 (Box I:A27, Reel 9)
      - Oct. 6-Nov. 6 (Box I:A28, Reel 10)
      - Nov. 7-Dec. 31 (Box I:A29, Reel 10)
    - 1831
      - Jan. 1-Mar.31
      - Apr. 2-June 19 (Box I:A30, Reel 11)
      - June 21-July 15 (Box I:A31, Reel 11)
      - July 16-Aug. 16 (Box I:A32, Reel 11)
      - Aug. 17-Sept. 15 (Box I:A33, Reel 12)
      - Sept. 16-Nov. 4 (Box I:A34, Reel 12)
      - Nov. 5-Dec. 14 (Box I:A35, Reel 12)
    - 1831, Dec. 15-1832, Jan. 18 (Box I:A36, Reel 13)
    - 1832 (Box I:A37, Reel 13)
      - Jan. 19-Feb. 22
      - Feb. 23-Apr. 5 (Box I:A38, Reel 13)
      - Apr. 6-May 14 (Box I:A39, Reel 14)
      - May 16-July 3 (Box I:A40, Reel 14)
      - July 4-22 (Box I:A41, Reel 14)
      - July 23-Aug. 8 (Box I:A42, Reel 15)
      - Aug. 9-Sept. 5 (Box I:A43, Reel 15)
      - Sept. 6-Oct. 4 (Box I:A44, Reel 15)
      - Oct. 5-Nov. 5 (Box I:A45, Reel 16)
    - 1832, Nov. 8-1833, Jan. 24 (Box I:A46, Reel 16)
    - 1833 (Box I:A47, Reel 16)
      - Jan. 25-Mar. 16
      - Mar. 18-Apr. 24 (Box I:A48, Reel 17)
      - Apr. 25-June 10 (Box I:A49, Reel 17)
      - June 11-July 15 (Box I:A50, Reel 17)
      - July 16-Aug. 6 (Box I:A51, Reel 18)
      - Aug. 7-Sept. 17 (Box I:A52, Reel 18)
      - Sept. 18-Oct. 15 (Box I:A53, Reel 18)
      - Oct. 16-Nov. 20 (Box I:A54, Reel 19)
      - Nov. 21-Dec. 30 (Box I:A55, Reel 19)
    - 1834 (Box I:A56 pt. 1, Reel 19)
      - Jan.-Apr.
        - A-C
        - D-H (Box I:A56 pt. 2, Reel 20)
        - J-W (Box I:A57, Reel 20)
      - May-Dec. (Box I:A58 pt. 1, Reel 20)
        - A-B
        - C-E (Box I:A58 pt. 2, Reel 21)
        - F-H (Box I:A58 pt. 3, Reel 21)
        - I-M (Box I:A59 pt. 1, Reel 21)
        - N-S (Box I:A59 pt. 2, Reel 22A)
        - S-Y (Box I:A59 pt. 3, Reel 22B)
    - 1835 (Box I:A60 pt. 1, Reel 22B)
      - Jan.-May
        - A-G
        - H-W (Box I:A60 pt. 2, Reel 23)
      - May-Aug. (Box I:A61 pt. 1, Reel 23)
        - A-F
        - G-M (Box I:A61 pt. 2, Reel 23)
        - N-W (Box I:A61 pt. 3, Reel 24)
      - Sept.-Dec. (Box I:A62 pt. 1, Reel 24)
        - A-G
        - H-W (Box I:A62 pt. 2, Reel 24)
    - 1836 (Box I:A63 pt. 1, Reel 25)
      - Jan.-Apr.
        - A-J
        - J-Z (Box I:A63 pt. 2, Reel 25)
      - May-Aug. (Box I:A64 pt. 1, Reel 25)
        - A-H
        - J-Z (Box I:A64 pt. 2, Reel 25)
      - Sept.-Dec. (Box I:A65 pt. 1, Reel 26)
        - A-G
        - H-W (Box I:A65 pt. 2, Reel 26)
    - 1837 (Box I:A66 pt. 1, Reel 26, Reel 27)
      - Jan.-Apr.
        - A-D
        - E-L (Box I:A66 pt. 2, Reel 27)
        - M-W (Box I:A66 pt. 3, Reel 27)
      - May-Sept. (Box I:A67 pt. 1, Reel 28)
        - A-G
        - H-W (Box I:A67 pt. 2, Reel 28)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Box I:A68, Reel 28)
        - A-W
    - 1838 (Box I:A69 pt. 1, Reel 29)
      - Jan.-June
        - A-G
        - H-Y (Box I:A69 pt. 2, Reel 29)
      - June-Sept. (Box I:A70 pt. 1, Reel 29)
        - A-H
        - J-W (Box I:A70 pt. 2, Reel 30)
      - Oct.-Dec. (Box I:A71 pt. 1, Reel 30)
        - A-G
        - H-W (Box I:A71 pt. 2, Reel 30)
    - 1839, Jan. 3-1842, Feb. 7 (Box I:A72 pt. 1, Reel 31)
    - 1839 (Box I:A73 pt. 1, Reel 31)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 9
      - Feb. 11-Mar. 30 (Box I:A73 pt. 2, Reel 31)
      - Apr. 1-May 13 (Box I:A74 pt. 1, Reel 32)
      - May 14-June 29 (Box I:A74 pt. 2, Reel 32)
      - July 1-31 (Box I:A75 pt. 1, Reel 32)
      - Aug. 1-Sept. 30 (Box I:A75 pt. 2, Reel 33A)
      - Oct. 2-Nov. 26 (Box I:A76 pt. 1, Reel 33A)
      - Nov. 27-Dec. 31 (Box I:A76 pt. 2, Reel 33A)
    - 1840 (Box I:A77 pt. 1, Reel 33B)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 1
      - Feb. 2-Mar. 30 (Box I:A77 pt. 2, Reel 34)
      - June 1-30 (nos. 1-90) (Box I:A78 pt. 1, Reel 34)
      - Apr. 1-10 (nos. 91-112)
      - Apr. 11-May 30 (nos. 113-229) (Box I:A78 pt. 2, Reel 34)
      - July 1-31 (Box I:A79 pt. 1, Reel 35)
      - Aug. 1-Sept. 29 (Box I:A79 pt. 2, Reel 35)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 24 (Box I:A80 pt. 1, Reel 35)
      - Nov. 25-Dec. 24 (Box I:A80 pt. 2, Reel 36)
    - 1841 (Box I:A81 pt. 1, Reel 37)
      - Jan. 4-Feb. 2
      - Feb. 3-Mar. 22 (Box I:A81 pt. 2, Reel 37)
      - Apr. 1-May 11 (Box I:A82 pt. 1, Reel 37)
      - May 12-June 29 (Box I:A82 pt. 2, Reel 37)
      - July 1-31 (Box I:A83 pt. 1)
      - Aug. 1-29 (Box I:A83 pt. 2, Reel 38)
      - Aug. 30-Sept. 30 (Box I:A83 pt. 3, Reel 38)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 15 (Box I:A84 pt. 1, Reel 38)
      - Nov. 16-Dec. 31 (Box I:A84 pt. 2, Reel 39)
    - 1842 (Box I:A85 pt. 1, Reel 39)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 11
      - Feb. 12-Mar. 31 (Box I:A85 pt. 2, Reel 39)
      - Apr. 1-May 17 (Box I:A86 pt. 1, Reel 40)
      - May 18-July 16 (Box I:A86 pt. 2, Reel 40)
      - July 1-Sept. 28 (Box I:A87, Reel 40)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 22 (Box I:A88 pt. 1, Reel 41)
      - Nov. 23-Dec. 31 (Box I:A88 pt. 2, Reel 41)
    - 1843 (Box I:A89 pt. 1, Reel 41)
      - Jan. 2-Feb. 14
      - Feb. 15- Mar. 31 (Box I:A89 pt. 2, Reel 41)
      - Apr. 1-June 8 (Box I:A90 pt. 1, Reel 42)
      - May 1- June 29 (Box I:A90 pt. 2, Reel 42)
      - June 1-Aug. 5 (Box I:A91 pt. 1, Reel 42)
      - Aug. 6-16 (Box I:A91 pt. 2, Reel 43)
      - Aug. 17-Nov. 10 (Box I:A92 pt. 1, Reel 43)
      - Nov. 11-Dec. 30 (Box I:A92 pt. 1, Reel 43)
    - 1844 (Box I:A93 pt. 1, Reel 44)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 15
      - Feb. 16-Mar. 30 (Box I:A93 pt. 2, Reel 44)
      - Apr. 1-June 29 (Box I:A94, Reel 44)
      - July 1-Sept. 30 (Box I:A95, Reel 45)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 29 (Box I:A96 pt. 1, Reel 45)
      - Nov. 30-Dec. 27 (Box I:A96 pt. 2, Reel 45)
    - 1844, Dec. 12-1845, Feb. 10 (Box I:A97 pt.1, Reel 46)
    - 1845 (Box I:A97 pt.2, Reel 46)
      - Feb. 11-Mar. 31
      - Jan. 8-June 30 (Box I:A98, Reel 46)
      - July 1-Aug. 15 (Box I:A99 pt. 1, Reel 47)
      - Aug. 16-Sept. 29 (Box I:A99 pt. 2, Reel 47)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 1 (Box I:A100 pt. 1, Reel 47)
      - Nov. 5-Dec. 31 (Box I:A100 pt. 2, Reel 48)
    - 1844, Dec. 2-1846, Feb. 9 (Box I:A101 pt. 1, Reel 48)
    - 1846 (Box I:A101 pt. 2, Reel 48)
      - Feb. 10-Mar. 30
      - Feb. 5-May 12 (Box I:A102 pt. 1, Reel 49)
      - May 13-June 30 (Box I:A102 pt. 2, Reel 49)
      - July 1-Aug. 17 (Box I:A103 pt. 1, Reel 49)
      - Aug. 18-Sept. 30 (Box I:A103 pt. 2, Reel 50)
      - Oct. 1-23 (Box I:A104 pt. 1, Reel 50)
      - Oct. 24-Nov. 24 (Box I:A104 pt. 2, Reel 50)
      - Nov. 25-Dec. 31 (Box I:A104 pt. 3, Reel 51)
    - 1847 (Box I:A105 pt. 1, Reel 51)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 10
      - Feb. 11-Mar. 31 (Box I:A105 pt. 2, Reel 51)
      - Jan. 20-May 10 (Box I:A106 pt. 1, Reel 52)
      - May 11-June 29 (Box I:A106 pt. 1, Reel 52)
      - Mar. 3-Sept. 16 (Box I:A107 pt. 1, Reel 52)
      - Aug. 1-31 (Box I:A107 pt. 2, Reel 53)
      - Sept. 17-30
      - Oct. 1-30 (Box I:A108 pt. 1, Reel 53)
      - Sept. 12-Oct. 30
      - Nov. 1-Dec. 3 (Box I:A108 pt. 2, Reel 53)
      - Dec. 4-31 (Box I:A108 pt. 3, Reel 54)
    - 1848 (Box I:A109 pt. 1, Reel 54)
      - Jan. 1-24
      - Jan. 25-Feb. 26 (Box I:A109 pt. 2, Reel 54)
      - Feb. 27- Mar. 31 (Box I:A109 pt. 3, Reel 55)
      - July 8-May 10 (Box I:A110 pt. 1, Reel 55)
      - May 11-June 30 (Box I:A110 pt. 2, Reel 55)
      - Feb. 18-July 26 (Box I:A111 pt. 1, Reel 56)
      - July 27-Aug. 28 (Box I:A111 pt. 2, Reel 56)
      - Aug. 29-Sept. 30 (Box I:A111 pt. 3, Reel 56)
      - May 29-Nov. 6 (Box I:A112 pt. 1, Reel 57)
      - Nov. 7-Dec. 4 (Box I:A112 pt. 2, Reel 57)
      - Dec. 5-30 (Box I:A112 pt. 3, Reel 57)
    - 1849 (Box I:A113 pt. 1, Reel 58)
      - Jan. 1-18
      - Jan. 19-Feb. 16 (Box I:A113 pt. 2, Reel 58)
      - Feb. 17-Mar. 31 (Box I:A113 pt. 3, Reel 58)
      - Apr. 2-May 8 (Box I:A114 pt. 1, Reel 59)
      - May 9-June 30 (Box I:A114 pt. 2, Reel 59)
      - July 1-Aug. 9 (Box I:A115 pt. 1, Reel 59)
      - Aug. 10-Sept. 30 (Box I:A115 pt. 2, Reel 60)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 19 (Box I:A116 pt. 1, Reel 60)
      - Nov. 20-Dec. 31 (Box I:A116 pt. 2, Reel 60)
    - 1850 (Box I:A117 pt. 1, Reel 61)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 25
      - Feb. 26-Mar. 30 (Box I:A117 pt. 2, Reel 61)
      - Apr. 1-May 17 (Box I:A118 pt. 1, Reel 62)
      - May 18- June 30 (Box I:A118 pt. 2, Reel 62)
      - July 1-Aug. 6 (Box I:A119 pt. 1, Reel 62)
      - Aug. 7-Sept. 30 (Box I:A119 pt. 2, Reel 63)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 16 (Box I:A120 pt. 1, Reel 63)
      - Nov. 18-Dec. 31 (Box I:A120 pt. 2, Reel 63)
    - 1851 (Box I:A121 pt. 1, Reel 64)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 5
      - Feb. 6-Mar. 31 (Box I:A121 pt. 2, Reel 64)
      - Apr. 1-May 8 (Box I:A122 pt. 1, Reel 64)
      - May 9-June 30 (Box I:A122 pt. 1, Reel 65)
      - July 1-Aug. 7 (Box I:A123 pt. 1, Reel 65)
      - Aug. 8-Sept. 30 (Box I:A123 pt. 2, Reel 65)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 21 (Box I:A124 pt. 1, Reel 66A)
      - Nov. 22-Dec. 31 (Box I:A124 pt. 2, Reel 66B)
    - 1852 (Box I:A125 pt. 1, Reel 66B)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 16
      - Feb. 17-Mar. 31 (Box I:A125 pt. 2, Reel 67)
      - Apr. 1-May 6 (Box I:A126 pt. 1, Reel 67)
      - May 7-June 30 (Box I:A126 pt. 2, Reel 67)
      - July 1-Aug. 11 (Box I:A127 pt. 1, Reel 68)
      - Aug. 12-Sept. 30 (Box I:A127 pt. 2, Reel 68)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 15 (Box I:A128 pt. 1, Reel 68)
      - Nov. 16-Dec. 31 (Box I:A128 pt. 2, Reel 69)
    - 1853 (Box I:A129 pt. 1, Reel 69)
      - Jan.1- Feb. 11
      - Feb. 12-Mar. 31 (Box I:A129 pt. 2, Reel 69)
      - Apr. 1-May 8 (Box I:A130 pt. 1, Reel 70)
      - May 9-June 30 (Box I:A130 pt. 2, Reel 70)
      - July 1-Aug. 9 (Box I:A131 pt. 1, Reel 70)
      - Aug. 10-Sept. 30 (Box I:A131 pt. 2, Reel 71)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 16 (Box I:A132 pt. 1, Reel 71)
      - Nov. 17-Dec. 31 (Box I:A132 pt. 2, Reel 71)
    - 1854 (Box I:A133 pt. 1, Reel 72)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 9
      - Feb. 10-Mar. 31 (Box I:A133 pt. 2, Reel 72)
      - Apr. 1-May 5 (Box I:A134 pt. 1, Reel 72)
      - May 6-June 30 (Box I:A134 pt. 2, Reel 73)
      - July 1-Aug. 11 (Box I:A135 pt. 1, Reel 73)
      - Aug. 12-Sept. 30 (Box I:A135 pt. 2, Reel 73)
      - R 74Oct. 1-Nov. 12 (Box I:A136 pt. 1, Reel 74)
      - Nov. 13-Dec. 30 (Box I:A136 pt. 2, Reel 74)
    - 1855 (Box I:A137 pt. 1, Reel 74)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 6
      - Feb. 7-Mar. 10 (Box I:A137 pt. 2, Reel 75)
      - Mar. 11-31 (Box I:A137 pt. 3, Reel 75)
      - Mar. 31-July 10 (Box I:A138, Reel 75)
      - Apr. 1-May 11 (Box I:A139 pt. 1, Reel 76)
      - May 12-June 30 (Box I:A139 pt. 2, Reel 76)
      - July 2-Aug. 7 (Box I:A140 pt. 1, Reel 77)
      - Aug. 8-Sept. 30 (Box I:A140 pt. 2, Reel 77)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 8 (Box I:A141 pt. 1, Reel 77)
      - Nov. 9-Dec. 31 (Box I:A141 pt. 2, Reel 78)
    - 1856 (Box I:A142 pt. 1, Reel 78)
      - Jan. 1-Feb. 18
      - Feb. 19-Mar. 31 (Box I:A142 pt. 2, Reel 78)
      - Apr. 1-May 9 (Box I:A143 pt. 1, Reel 79)
      - May 10-June 30 (Box I:A143 pt. 2, Reel 79)
      - July 1-Sept. 30 (Box I:A144, Reel 80)
      - Oct. 1-Nov. 14 (Box I:A145 pt. 1, Reel 80)
      - Nov. 15-Dec. 31 (Box I:A145 pt. 2, Reel 81)
    - 1857 (Box I:A146 pt. 1, Reel 81)